ntotank.com 2019-01-19

# Privacy Policy

_Last updated: December 06, 2015_

## Foreword Statement

  * We _do not_ keep credit card, debit, or bank account numbers on our server. 
  * We _do not_ sell your information to other companies. 
  * We _are happy_ to assist you over the phone at [(888) 686-8265](tel:8886868265). 

National Tank Outlet, LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates the [NTOTank.com](https://www.ntotank.com/) e-commerce store and website (the "E-commerce Site").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our E-commerce Site.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the E-commerce Site. By using the E-commerce Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our [Terms of Service](https://www.ntotank.com/tos-policy).

## Security

We use an Extended Validation [2048-bit encrypted root certificate](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Key_size) issued by [DigiCert Inc](https://www.digicert.com/about-digicert.htm). DigiCert is one of the world’s most trusted authorities in [website encryption](https://www.digicert.com/news/DigiCert_PCI_White_Paper.pdf). NTOTank.com uses the latest in [Transport Layer Security](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security) (1.2 TLS) with [128-bit AES encryption](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Advanced_Encryption_Standard) for sending and receiving information through an [HTTPS protocol](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTPS).

Personal information provided on the website and online credit card transactions are transmitted through a secure server. We do not save credit card numbers on our server. We are committed to handling your personal information with responsibility and security. We take appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative steps to maintain the security and accuracy of personally identifiable information we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. Our website uses Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption technology to protect your personal information during data transport. TLS encrypts ordering information such as your name, address, and credit card number.

## Information Collection And Use

While using our E-commerce Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, payment information, other information ("Personal Information").

We collect this information for the purpose of providing the E-commerce Site, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests / inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services. We do not save debit card, credit card, or bank account numbers on our server.

## Log Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our E-commerce Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our E-commerce Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our E-commerce Site's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our E-commerce Site.

A "web beacon" or "pixel tag" or "clear gif" is typically a one-pixel image, used to pass information from your computer or mobile device to a website. We recommend calling us at [(888) 686-8265](tel:8886868265) if you wish to avoid being tracked by Web Beacons.

We use cookies and web beacons to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to the website as well as to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the website you visited immediately before clicking to the NTOTank.com website. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions. You can, of course, disable cookies and web beacons on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of our website will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. We may also use web beacons, and other technologies, to help track whether our communications are reaching you, to measure their effectiveness, or to collect certain non-personal information about your computer, device, or browser in order to allow us to better design future communications to you.

We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and web beacons and collect information on our behalf or provide services such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional services, or data management. These third parties are prohibited from sharing your information with anyone other than the National Tank Outlet.

## Account Registration

To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register on the NTOTank.com website. As a registered customer, you only have to enter your shipping addresses and billing information once; they will be securely stored with us or PayPal, for your future use. Using your name and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete, or change information.

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to log out at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.

## Remarketing

National Tank Outlet, LLC uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you have visited our E-commerce Site. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our E-commerce Site. We may use several remarketing services including Google, Yahoo, Bing, Adroll, Perfect Audience, and others.

## Analytics and Ad Serving

We use analytics and ad services to create and optimize advertising campaigns. Analytics helps us identify important pages and products on our website, as well as consumer trends.

### Google

Google Analytics Google AdWords are tracking and advertising services provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by visiting the [Google Ads Settings page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Google also recommends installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the [Google Privacy & Terms page](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Yahoo

Yahoo Web Analytics and Yahoo Gemini are tracking and advertising services provided by Yahoo Inc.

You can opt-out of the Yahoo Ad Interest Manager by visiting <https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/>

### Bing

Bing Universal Event Tracking and Bing Ads are tracking and advertising services provided by Microsoft Corporation.

You can opt-out of Bing Interest-Based Ads by visiting <https://choice.microsoft.com/en-US/opt-out>

### ZopIM

ZopIM is live chat software by Zendesk, Inc that facilitates communication between National Tank Outlet and customers at NTOTank.com. ZopIM tracks user activity across the NTOTank.com website whether or not chat is engaged. As of right now there is no way to disable this tracking without breaking the website. We recommend calling us [(888) 686-8265](tel:8886868265) to complete your order if this is a concern.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our E-commerce Site, to perform E-commerce Site-related services, and to assist us in analyzing how our E-commerce Site is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

## Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

### MailChimp

MailChimp is an email communication tool that manages customer email lists and newsletters for National Tank Outlet. Read about their security by visiting <http://mailchimp.com/about/security/>. You can opt out of all newsletter and email notifications by visiting [http://ntotank.us1.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=68c0a8055d1beb38575b119a5&id=02b50c3afc](http://ntotank.us1.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=68c0a8055d1beb38575b119a5&id=02b50c3afc). Please note, this will not exclude you from receiving receipts or direct communication from sales representatives regarding orders.

## Compliance With Laws

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena, or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement.

## Business Transaction

If National Tank Outlet, LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred as a business asset. In such cases, we will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred to another business.

## International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links To Other Sites

Our E-commerce Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's Privacy

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our E-commerce Site. Our E-commerce Site does not address anyone under the age of 17 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 17. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from children under age 17 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please send us an email to [sales@ntotank.com](mailto:sales@ntotank.com) and allow for 14 business days for a response.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 6, 2015 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the E-commerce Site after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

National Tank Outlet  
4728 Spottswood Ave, Ste 328  
Memphis, TN 38117
